<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Patient Management</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">open_drawer</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">close_drawer</string>

    <!-- Navigation Drawer menu labels -->
    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_make_appointment">Make Appointment</string>
    <string name="nav_patient_management">Patient Management</string>
    <string name="nav_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="nav_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="nav_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="nav_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="nav_health">Health Tips</string>
    <string name="nav_patho">Pathology Labs</string>
    <string name="nav_blood">Blood Banks</string>


    <!-- Toolbar titles when navigation menu item is selected -->
    <string-array name="nav_item_activity_titles">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Make Appointment</item>
        <item>Patient Management</item>
        <item>Health Tips</item>
        <item>Pathology Labs</item>
        <item>Blood Banks</item>
        <item>Notifications</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
        <item>Profile</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="android_dropdown_arrays">
        <item>Eye</item>
        <item>Orthopedics</item>
        <item>Dentist</item>
        <item>Cardiology</item>
        <item>Neurology</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="blood_group_array">
        <item>O−</item>
        <item>O+</item>
        <item>A−</item>
        <item>A+</item>
        <item>B-</item>
        <item>B+</item>
        <item>AB−</item>
        <item>AB+</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="action_clear_all">Clear All</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="action_mark_all_read">Mark All as Read</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="action_refresh">Refresh</string>


    <string name="text_content">Demo Details </string>


    <string name="changelog_Header">ChangeLog</string>


    <!-- About -->
    <string name="title_about"><![CDATA[
            <b>ChangeLog Library</b>&nbsp;<font color="#888888">v%1$s</font>
        ]]></string>

    <string name="about_ok">OK</string>

    <string name="changelog_body">

        <b><u>PM 2.1 - Changes:</u></b>\n
        &#8226; New Tabs Added. \n
        &#8226; Blood Bank working with Requests. \n
        &#8226; Pathological Labs Implemented. \n\n

        <b><u>PM 2.0 - Changes:</u></b>\n
        &#8226; About us &amp; Privacy Policy page Completed \n
        &#8226; OTA update Enabled \n\n

        <b><u>PM 1.9 - Changes:</u></b>\n
        &#8226; Settings Tab will check for Updates and Changelog will Show There \n
        &#8226; Login User image will show in Navigation Drawer Header \n
        &#8226; Doctor Images Redesigned \n
        &#8226; Sign up, Login, ForgetPassword pages Should Works As Should be. [ There are Some Code Glitches ] \n
        &#8226; User Name will show in Navigation Drawer. \n \n

        <b><u>PM 1.8 - Changes:</u></b>\n
         &#8226; App size reduce from 12 MB to 5 MB.\n
         &#8226; All &amp; and Images Stored in Server \n
         &#8226; Forget Password Implemented.\n \n

        <b><u>PM 1.7 - Changes:</u></b>\n
         &#8226; Redesign Appointment Layout &amp; Appointment can be deleted [ On Tap ] \n\n
         &#8226; Some Icon changed\n

        <b><u>PM 1.5 - Changes:</u></b>\n
         &#8226; Make Appointment is Working. \n
         \ **go to Patient Management. then select Your Appointment \n \n

        <b><u>PM 1.2 - Changes:</u></b>\n
        &#8226; New Personal Info Tab added. \n\n

        <b><u>PM 1.1 - Changes:</u></b>\n
        &#8226; Login &amp; Sign up page Completed. \n
        &#8226; Layout fix for small screen device(Sudipto) \n
        &#8226; Logout button working. \n
        &#8226; User Name will show in Navigation Drawer. \n \n
        <b><u>PM 1.0 - Changes:</u></b>\n

        &#8226; A Static login page is created (not connected to any database) \n
        &#8226; Login id= admin &amp; pass=admin \n
        &#8226; Sign up page has been added. but its just a template. nothing to work. and *May be Crash your application* \n
        &#8226; App Logo is Created. \n
        \n



</string>

    <string name="information_about_you">
        We may collect information from you under the following circumstances.\n \n

        \ \ &#8226; If you fill out and submit a form on the website.\n
        \ \ &#8226; If you access password restricted access areas of the website. Users may be identified by their login credentials. This information will only be used to direct users to the correct area of the website and to improve site content and usability.\n
        \ \  &#8226; If you voluntarily provide information to us through email correspondence or by phone.
    </string>
    <string name="Who_We_Share_Your_Information_With">
        We do not share personal information with third parties nor do we store any information about your visit to this website other than to analyse and optimise our content through the use of cookies.\n \n
        You can turn off the use of cookies at anytime by changing your specific browser settings
    </string>
    <string name="Changes_To_This_Privacy_Statement">
        We may change this privacy policy at any time. Whenever we revise this privacy policy, we will change the date on the notice to indicate when revisions were made.
        By using our website and/or submitting personal information to us, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy as stated at the time you use the website and/or at the time you submit your personal information
    </string>
    <string name="Privacy_Policy_1st_paragraph">
        We, at Patient Management Healthcare, are committed to protecting your privacy. \n\n
        This privacy policy gives you information as to the types of personal information we collect, how we use that information and whom we may share it with.
    </string>


    <string name="home_test_text">Tata Main Hospital, the Medical Division of Tata Steel and its nine dispensaries at Jamshedpur provide curative healthcare services to the employees of Tata Steel and their families free of cost.
        Apart from TMH and the dispensaries, out-location hospitals are located at Jamadoba, Noamundi and Sukhinda Mines and West Bokaro Collieries.
        TMH also extends its facilities to non-entitled patients from Jamshedpur and its surrounding area.Tata Main Hospital, the Medical Division of Tata Steel
        and its nine dispensaries at Jamshedpur provide curative healthcare services to the employees
        of Tata Steel and their families free of cost.
        Apart from TMH and the dispensaries, out-location hospitals are located at Jamadoba, Noamundi and Sukhinda Mines and West Bokaro Collieries.
        TMH also extends its facilities to non-entitled patients from Jamshedpur and its surrounding area.Tata Main Hospital, the Medical Division of Tata Steel
        and its nine dispensaries at Jamshedpur provide curative healthcare services to the employees
        of Tata Steel and their families free of cost. Apart from TMH
        and the dispensaries, out-location hospitals are located at Jamadoba, Noamundi and Sukhinda Mines and West Bokaro Collieries. TMH also extends its facilities to non-entitled patients from Jamshedpur and its surrounding area.
        Tata Main Hospital, the Medical Division of Tata Steel and its nine dispensaries at Jamshedpur provide curative healthcare services to the employees of Tata Steel and their families free of cost. Apart from TMH and the dispensaries,
        out-location hospitals are located at Jamadoba, Noamundi and Sukhinda Mines and West Bokaro Collieries. TMH also extends its facilities to non-entitled patients from Jamshedpur and its surrounding area.Tata Main Hospital, the Medical Division
        of Tata Steel and its nine dispensaries at Jamshedpur provide curative healthcare services to the employees of Tata Steel and their families free of cost. Apart from TMH and the dispensaries, out-location hospitals are located
        at Jamadoba, Noamundi and Sukhinda Mines and West Bokaro Collieries. TMH also extends its facilities to non-entitled patients from Jamshedpur and its surrounding area. Tata Main Hospital, the Medical Division of Tata Steel and its nine dispensaries
        at Jamshedpur provide curative healthcare services to the employees of Tata Steel and their families free of cost. Apart from TMH and the dispensaries, out-location hospitals are located at Jamadoba, Noamundi and Sukhinda Mines and West Bokaro Collieries.
        TMH also extends its facilities to non-entitled patients from Jamshedpur and its surrounding area.</string>
    <string name="demo">DEMO</string>


</resources>
